Bell Brothers Collection
Bell Brothers Collection
- Audiotapes
  - Schwanda, Weinberger; Stone Guest, Don Juan; Dargomizhsky, Piano Concerto, Hiller; Alessandro Moreski, Castrato singer, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_335; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Schweitzer Interview; Perry Como TV Show; La Traviata, 05/21/1964; 01/11/1964; bell_brothers_tapes_681; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Seasons (Haydn) Love of a Kings (Montemezzi) - Judy Garland TV, 02/25/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_342; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Semiramide Joan (Rossini) - Sutherland - Fernando De Lucia - S. Lemeshev - F. Firsova - E. Bilov - Holy Week in Malaga- Il Duello (Paisiello), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_610; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Semyon Kotko; (Prokofieff) - Liars (jones) -Piotr Zak - Intern Festival (Stravinsky Concert), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_594; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Seven Sinners; Perry Como; Justice W. O. Douglas; Old Lady Shows her Medals; Bob Scobey; Vanni; Marcoux, 06/12/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_647; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Shell Chateau Radio; Prof. A. Toynbee; Cyril Richard and Hermione Baddeley, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_450; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Shell Chateau Radio; W. Beery; Perry Como, 06/06/1962; 10/12/1935; 11/30/1935; 12/21/1935; bell_brothers_tapes_451; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Shell Chateau Radio Programs (Al Jolson), 08/03/1935; 08/10/1935; 08/17/1935; bell_brothers_tapes_372; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Shell Chateau Radio Shows - Wallace Beery; Suite #3 (Tchaikovsky) Turandot (Conclusion), 12/07/1935; 12/14/1935; bell_brothers_tapes_427; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - Shell Chateau Radio Shows: Al Jolson; Shell Chateau, 08/31/1935; 09/07/1935; 09/21/1935; 09/28/1935; bell_brothers_tapes_438; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Shell Chateau Radio; Duke Ellington; Carry Moore; TV Perry Como, 11/16/1935; 11/23/1935; 05/09/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_416; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Sherlock Holmes; Cant Help Singing; King John, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_215; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Siberia, Giordano; Ressurezzione, Alfano, Records; Susannah, Floyd; Quartets, Bloch, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_390; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Siddhartha Herman Hesse, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_251; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Siddhartha Herman Hesse, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_252; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Siddhartha Herman Hesse, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_253; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Siegfried, Bayreuth Festival, (Part 1), 1960; bell_brothers_tapes_124; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Siegfried, Bayreuth Festival, (Part 2), 1960; bell_brothers_tapes_125; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Simon Boccanegra, Verdi, (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_060; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - Simon Boccanegra, Verdi, (Part 2), (Conclusion), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_061; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - Simply Heavenly with lyrics by Langston Hughes, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_005; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Singing Fishing Ernst Krenek, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_235; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Slavenski, Victoria; Laudi; Palestrina; B. Goodman, Vocals; Hollywood Actors; Perry Como; Habanero, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_552; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Slightly French Gentlemen Marry Brunettes; Der Hausliche Krieg (Schubert) Allez -Hop (Berio); Impresario (Mozart); Medieval Music; John McCormack, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_157; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Socrate Immaginario (Paisiello) Bertrand Russell - Jazz Band (Film), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_460; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Sonata in G - Piano Quartet by Lekeu - George Gershwin Tribute - Carnegie Hall, 03/18/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_433; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - Song to remember Philomen and Baucis (Haydn) - Turandot, 12/09/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_341; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Sonnambula (Conclusion) Flying Dutchman Metropolitan Too Much Harmony (Bing Crosby), 02/02/1963; 1933; bell_brothers_tapes_590; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Sophie (S. Allen) Hot Spot (J. Holiday), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_672; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Sorochintsy Fair - Mussorgsky Down Argentine Way - G. Anedda: Mandolin, 03/17/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_276; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Sounds of Animals; China Gate, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_443; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Spanisches Liederbuch, Wolf; John Ch. Thomas, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_173; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Spanish Poetry; Enchanted Nutcracker; O'Henry Stories; V. Lopes; Spellman, Rachmaninoff; Gregorian Chants; Saintmakers Xmas Eve, N. Dello Joio, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_388; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Spontini, Mahler; Eisenhower; Walter; Carstairs, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_540; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Sports Awards 60; President Kennedy on UN, Adlai Stevenson at UN; B. Russell and C. P. Snow, J. Huguet, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_384; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - St. John Passion (Heinrich Schuetz) - R. Shaw Chorale - Zero Mostel - P. Como, 04/10/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_597; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - St. Mathews Passion, Bach, D. Fischer-Dieskau, (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_200; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - St. Mathews Passion, Bach, D. Fischer-Dieskau, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_201; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - St. Matthew Passion (Bach) - White Devil (Webster); Easter Liturgy (II) -- (Gregorian), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_591; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Stars and Stripes Forever, Sousa; Heifetz, Reimers; Truman; Vogelhandler, Zeller; Star Maker; Sepolcro, Ziani, 06/22/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_493; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Steiner Film Music; Seem My Lawyer; Captain Blood; Dolly Sisters; Big Hewer; Vespers, Monteverdi, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_620; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Stokowski Rehearsal Shakespeare - September Psalmi (Lassus) - Prokofieff I Film - Emilio de Gogorza, 06/15/1963; 06/16/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_602; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Storia Della Musica Italiana, Anthology; Marcella Sembrich; Story of the Atom, Lord Rutherford, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_621; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Storia Della Musica Italiana, Volume II (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_678; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Storia Della Musica Italiana, Volume III (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_680; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Storia Della Musica Italiana, Volume III (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_679; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Stronger (Weingall) Perry Como; Hitler; O'Pratori; D Huvium Universale (Carissi mi) - Les Brigands (Offenbach), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_422; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - Sun Valley Serenade - Trial of Lucullu - Trial of Eichmann - 20th Century - Munich, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_283; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Sweethearts (Eddy - Macdonald) (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_216; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Sweethearts (Eddy - Macdonald) (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_217; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Symphonies # 5 and 9, Beethoven-Menglbrg TV Telethon; Rose of Washington Square, Jolson, Ch. Lindbergh, P. Faith; Rey de la Torre, Symphony #2, Walton, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_347; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Symphonies No. 26; 36; 54; 70, Haydn; Paris, Mozart, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_517; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Symphonies No. 46; 52; 67; 53, Haydn, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_518; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Symphonies No. 7 and 8, Haydn; E. Pinza, Flutes; Werner Von Braum, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_571; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Symphony #6 (Miaskovsky)- Miscellaneous Forgotten Music Toscanini etc., undated; bell_brothers_tapes_343; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Symphony No. 10, Mahler, Carnegie Hall; Violin Concerto, Mozart; Kreisler, 03/16/1958; bell_brothers_tapes_471; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Symphony No. 3, Enesco; M. Monroe; Wingless Victory; Hudson Hoagland; Mystere des Saints Innocents, Barraud; Daddy do I dare Eat a Peach, T. S. Eliot; Symphony No. 10, Mehler, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_501; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Symphony No. 8, Mahler; Coq DOr, Rimsky-Korsakoff; W. Rogers; Irma Kolassi; Clark Terry Sextet, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_560; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Tacoma Bridge; Marine Corps; Nina Simone; Krupp Works; Rickenbacker; Mac Kenzie King; Jimmy Walker; Vis. Montgomery; Doll Face, Perry Como, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_441; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Tall, Dark and Handsome; When Johnny Comes; Marching Home; Out of this World; Young Abe Lincoln, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_101; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - Tammy Grimes Eddie Albert, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_074; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - Elizabeth, Queen of England, Rossini; Budapest Piano Composer; Hootenanny; Voice of Firestone, F. Correlli; Freedom Now, Birmingham Ala. Integration Movement., Von Braun Biography; Four Feathers Film; The Deserteur, Monsigny; Boris Christoff; Rev. R. Abernathy; Savitri, Holst; Having a Wonderful Time; Carmen; Rhythm of the Range (Tapes 547 NS 345A), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_623; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Tea for Two (Concluded) - Delightfully Dangerous - Soviet Schoolteacher -Great Rupert - Babes On Broadway - Star Spangled Rhythm, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_281; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Tennessee Williams Plays - TV, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_233; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Thanks a Million; Greenwich Village, Symphony No. 8, V. Williams; Il Conte Ory, Rossini; Explorers, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_526; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - The Apostles (Elgar) - Le Coq D'Or (Rimsky-Korsakoff) - Il Mondo della Luna (Haydn), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_315; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - The Barbered Bride, Smetana, Maria Chamber, 05/08/1937; bell_brothers_tapes_059; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - The Creation (Haydn); San Francisco; Shall We Dance; Always Leave Them Laughing; John McCormack, 05/23/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_158; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - The Fiery Angel, Prokofieff; Perry Como; Betty Grable; Brenda Lee, (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_062; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - The Great Waltz, Miliza Korjus, 1938; bell_brothers_tapes_107; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - The Guardsman, Lunt and Fontanne, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_110; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - The Iceman Cometh, O'Neill; 4 hours, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_108; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - The King Steps Out Grace Moore - Film, 04/26/1959; "bell_brothers_tapes_022 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - The Magic Bow, Paganin-Menuhim, Film, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_076; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - The Mother of Us All, Virgil Thomson; Gertrude Stein, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_673; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - The Seagull (Chekhov), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_072; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - The Secret, Smetana, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_146; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - The Sky's the Limit - Reveille With Beverly - Richard Tauber- The Goon Show- Maria Galvany- Cesare Formichi, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_284; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - The Sky's the Limit Fred Astaire, 1943; bell_brothers_tapes_014; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Therese Raquin Emilem Zola TV, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_244; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Third Man George London - Ricardo Stracciari - Hope - Sinatra - Lamor - Abraham and The Angel (Delannoy) Hollywood Blvd. - Night Song, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_434; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - Thomas Mann - In a series of lectures from the Library of Congress, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_263; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Those Ragtime Years (Hoagy Carmichael), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_133; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Till the Clouds Roll By - Gen. Pershing - Benny Goodman - Dusolina Giannini - Folk Singers - Yom Kippur Services (Jan Peerce) - Sea Chanties, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_264; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Tolstoy - H. Keller - Dr. R. Barker - Joyce Grenfell- Historic Music (English Houses), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_584; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Tommy Dorsey, Count Basie, and Benny Goodman broadcasts, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_002; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Toni Dal Monte- Elisabeth Schumann; Ignace Paderewski; Renato Zanelli Lycidas, John Gielgud, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_204; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Tosca Met; Tenor (wedeking) Madrigals - C.H. Lindbergh - Biography, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_432; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - Tosca, Film; Bernstein, L. Lenya; Step Lively, Elena Geerhardt; Protagonist, Weill, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_407; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Tosca; Vespri Siciliani; Magic Flute, 01/23/1955; 01/15/1956; bell_brothers_tapes_445; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Toscanini - H. Ford Sr. A Huxley - Labyrinth (Menotti) - Lucia Adam. Rosenthal- Saxes - Clarinets, 1937; bell_brothers_tapes_581; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Toscanini - R. Creeley - Metropolitan Opera Jazz Concert - Vienna Choir Boys - Voice of Firestone - Senator Goldwater, 03/31/1963; 04/07/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_595; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Toscanini; Schoenberg - Davies - L. Armstrong - D Day Hootenanny - Political Figures - Max Ferguson - Automobile Sounds - Marilyn Monroe, 07/06/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_615; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Toscanini Broadcast - Singers NBC, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_664; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Toscanini Radio Broadcasts, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_345; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Toscanini Radio Broadcasts, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_346; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Toscanini, High Noon; Notorious; Erwartung, Gluck; Attraverso Lo Specchio, Castiglioni; Glueckliche Hand, Gluck, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_568; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Toscanini, Moses and Aaron, Schoenberg, Philharmonic Hall Concert, New York; Hootenanny; The Devil Take her, Benjamin; Cydalise et le Chevre Pied, Pierne, 11/26/1983; 04/27/1963; 04/28/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_650; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Toscanini; Beatrice and Benedict, Berlioz, B. Ruth; Hunter College Concert, J. Dos Passos, B. Ruth, 02/04/1939; 06/09/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_619; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Toscanini; Girl of the Golden West, Tebaldi, RAI; S. Gazzelloni, Flute; Story of Mozart, Film, 02/12/1938; bell_brothers_tapes_558; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Toscanini; Tribute to Duke Ellington, Carnegie Hall; Galileo-Galilei, Brecht; Hallelujah, Film, Spivey; Perry Como; Van Cliburn (Festival), 11/19/1938; 11/14/1953; 05/01/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_645; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Town Hall of Air Telethon; E. Kovacs; Marcel Wittrisch; Josh White; Brothers Four, etc, 11/28/1940; 01/23/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_419; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Tragodie salome (Schmitt) - Beecham M. Ghandi - E. Waters Diamond Horse Shoe - D. Shore, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_395; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Traviata Metropolitan Gertz - Dalyrac, Etc., 03/16/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_576; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Traviata, Verdi, Metropolitan, (Part 1), 03/06/1937; bell_brothers_tapes_169; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box box 13)
  - Traviata, Verdi, Metropolitan, (Part 2), 03/06/1937; bell_brothers_tapes_170; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box box 13)
  - Tribute to Jerome Kern, All Star, CBS, 1946; bell_brothers_tapes_654; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Tribute to Stark Young; P. Como; Babe Ruth; Gen Patton - Igor Sikorsky - G. Whalen, 03/06/1963; 03/20/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_582; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Tristan and Isolde, Metropolitan; Billy Mitchell; Weekend in Havana, A. Faye, 02/23/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_556; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Trovatore (Metropolitan Opera), 01/11/1941; bell_brothers_tapes_078; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - Trovatore (Metropolitan); Missa Nativitate Scarlatti; Road to Bali (Crosby - Hope- Lamour) Classical Singers, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_079; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - Turandot Puccini, Metropolitan (Nilsson) (Part 1), 03/04/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_193; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Turandot Puccini, Metropolitan (Nilsson) (Part 2), 03/04/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_194; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Twain, Mark; Toscanini; Glenn Milller, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_684; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Two Girls and a Sailor and Lotte Lehman Interview, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_687; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Two Girls and a Sailor and Lotte Lehman Interview, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_688; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - U-2 Affair, Miscellaneous Personalities, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_332; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Una Gita in Campagna (Peragallo); Il Mantello Chailly; Quartet (Gounod); Quartet (Donizetti), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_189; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Una Notte In Paradiso (Bucchi) Tornai Mass, undated; "bell_brothers_tapes_051 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Up in Central Park; Kovantschina; La Cinesi, Gluck; Nineteen Century Choral Music, Grieg; Berlioz; Cornelius; Stamford; Town Hall Concert; Mass Benedictus; Torneo Notturno, Malipiero, 10/23/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_675; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Vanessa, Barber; Merchant of Venice, Castelnuovo; Tedesco; Calamity Jane, D. Day; McGuire Sisters, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_520; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Variety Girl Crosby - Hope, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_228; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Verdi - Metropolitan Rigoletto Jussi Bjoerling, 12/25/1948; "bell_brothers_tapes_045 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Victor Borge, Jack Benny, C. Nielsen; Bobby Breen; Chamberlain, Bell Telephone Hour, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_304; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles (Festival), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_084; 1/2 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - Victory at Sea, TV version, edited, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_111; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - Vienna - Festival - Vivaldi - Nina Koshets - Hootenanny; Aloma of the South Seas (Dorothy Lamour) Jesu Christo (H. Schuetz) -Everyman, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_644; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - Viola Concerto (Martinu) Fritz Kreisler - John McCormack, 01/06/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_375; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Voices of Former Presidents and Candidates; Dracula Orson Wells - Concluded, 1938; 10/06/1933; bell_brothers_tapes_658; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Volpone, Burt; River of No Return, Marilyn Monroe; I'll Take romance, Grace Moore; Ad. Byrd; E. Adams; Broadway to Hollywood, Duke E., undated; bell_brothers_tapes_522; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Waiting for Godot (Z. Mostel), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_239; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Wake Up and Live; Meet Me in St. Louis (Garland); Words and Music; Trojans at Carthage (Berlitz), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_691; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Wake Up and Live; Meet Me in St. Louis (Garland); Words and Music; Trojans at Carthage (Berlitz), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_692; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Walkure Cranks - A. Moffo- H.P. Long - Segovia - W. Landowska - James Joyce, 1937; bell_brothers_tapes_579; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - War requiem, TV, Britten; Liszt; Rossini; G. Marx; Der Liebesverbot, Wagner; ASCAP, Twenty fifth Anniversary, 09/24/1940; bell_brothers_tapes_652; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - William Tell (Rossini) - Thomas Mann - Scotch Songs - Gen. Wain Wright - violinists, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_258; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Winston Churchill; Richard Burton - Memoirs; Perry Como; Chet Huntley; Ginny Tiu, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_066; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - Works by Ernest Berwald - Richard Tauber - On an Island with you - Seven days leave Lelio (Berlioz) - Nina Simone, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_289; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Wozzeck, Berg; Recruiting Sergeant, Dublin, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_199; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Yerma, Apivor; Joan Sutherland; Celestina Boninsegna; Wild Duck, Ibsen; McGuire Sisters, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_525; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - You cant have everything Film - Clarence Ashley - King Roger (K. Szymanowski) Perry Como, 05/23/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_423; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - You cant have everything Film - Clarence Ashley - King Roger (K. Szymanowski) Perry Como, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_424; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - You'll Find Out; Carnival in Costa Rica; Cosi Fan Tutte, Metropolitan; Leadbelly, 04/14/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_415; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - You're a Sweetheart - G. Burns - Bernard Baruch - Mayor of 44 ST - Tea for Two - 52 St, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_280; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Ziegfeld Follies (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_213; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Ziegfeld Follies (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_214; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Ziegfeld Girl (#1) - Edison - F.D.R. - Great Victor Herbert - I Due Foscari (Verdi), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_428; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)